{
    "id": "3f9200a37ab74992a0c8c4c9bb79d803",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He promised that he would help me but let me ………………… as usual.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will let you …………………. a secret. Mary is seeing a friend of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He might ask but don’t let …………………. that you know where John is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She refused to let me …………………. the house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He let ................................................. a big scream when his cut his finger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Thanks to his good conduct, he was let ............................................... jail three years early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out of",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t know what I was letting myself .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in for",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "As I had lost my keys, I couldn’t let myself ………………… my flat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "on to",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He thought he would be let ………………… but the judge sent him to jail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain didn’t let .......................................... all day we couldn’t even go for a walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}